Devin Hamid

14551 Fremont Ave. N. Shoreline, WA 98133 (206) 919-2267 DevinLeigh@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced form designer with considerable database experience, customer service skills, and a background in project coordination. Demonstrated track record of successfully organizing the form development process for over 40 clinical protocols from inception to activation.

Skills

Highly organized and skilled at prioritizing and multitasking in environments where attention to detail and time-sensitivity are crucial.

Excellent customer service ethic. Able to assess a client's needs and if confronted with a potentially contentious situation, address and diffuse issues calmly before they escalate.

Efficient comprehension of Windows-based computer software, Microsoft Word and Excel, as well as familiarity with Oracle® databases, Medidata Rave®, Toad™ and Teleform® software and basic understanding of SQL scripts and writing HTML.

Employment

Case Report Forms Designer
Contract Employee
Cancer Research and Biostatistics, Seattle, Washington

2009 - 2013

2014 - present

Provide general oversight of the process of developing forms to be used by medical professionals administering cancer research studies that are facilitated by SWOG.

Work directly with statisticians, programmers and study coordinators to ensure deadlines are met in accordance with study activation dates. Utilize creativity and an eye for detail to design new forms to match the specifications given by statisticians and ensure that the form's data is correctly transferred to the database upon form submission. Maintain database tables and file system for form and study attributes.

Available to respond to the needs of all parties involved in a form's activation and recognized for my speed, efficiency, attention to detail and discretion in the process.

Data Coordinator Cancer Research and Biostatistics, Seattle, Washington

2006 - 2009

Acted as liaison and reference resource to Clinical Research Associates and other project personnel at participating cancer research study sites across the U.S. and Canada. Responsible for answering questions in a courteous, professional and timely manner via phone and email.

Responsible for handling confidential study participant information with discretion and careful attention to accuracy.

Performed quality control review of study data and assisted in the review of electronic data and document management systems.

Administrative Assistant The Rockefeller Foundation, New York, New York

2005 - 2006

Performed clerical duties such as answering calls, scheduling meetings and filing as needed.

Data Control Technician Cancer Research and Biostatistics, Seattle, Washington

2004 - 2005

Supported the flow and entry of clinical patient data. Scanned and verified electronically imaged data forms used in cancer research studies, abstracted and entered data off of paper forms, redacted confidential information submitted in error, routed incoming calls, performed patient registrations and aided in the design of forms to be used in future studies.

Receptionist 2003 - 2004

Fishing Company of Alaska, Seattle, Washington

Performed front desk duties such as answering phones and directing calls, sorting mail, greeting clients, and various other activities as needed by office personnel.

Instructor 2002, 2003

Idaho Shakespeare Festival, Boise, Idaho

Taught pre-school through high-school aged children games and exercises to familiarize them with basic concepts and benefits of theatre. Co-directed a Shakespearean play performed by eighth and ninth graders.

2002 Actor

Theatre IV, Richmond, Virginia

Performed as an actor in a 2-play repertoire of children's theatre to grades kindergarten through high school throughout Virginia.

Acted as the Secretary and Treasurer for my cast of 3 actors, keeping track of all expenses and balancing costs with our account of petty cash as well as updating a daily record of mileage and events.

Intern 2000 - 2001

Company of Fools, Hailey, Idaho

Worked in all capacities of the non-profit theatre company, including office work (filing, copying, data entry, research, mailing, promotion, acknowledging donors, etc.) and stage production elements (stage managing, prop gathering, set building, acting as stage hand, performing). Worked as a manager of the company's theater while no plays were being produced and it was used as a movie house. Sold tickets, balanced the registers and calculated the night's gross income for the film distribution companies.

Began as a summer intern and was asked to stay through the following season. Asked to extend my contract once more to manage the box office and staff for the production of True West starring Bruce Willis.

Education Boise State University, Boise, Idaho

B.A., Theatre Performance and Direction, Minor in Communication

Magna Cum Laude graduate

Brown Dean's Scholarship recipient: Theatre Arts Department Scholarship recipient BSU Theatre Majors Association – Treasurer/Secretary, 1998-1999